<resources>
    <string name="app_name">30DaysTips</string>
    <string name="version">Version: %.1f</string>
    <string name="icons">Icons by</string>
    <string name="icons_title">Icons8</string>
    <string name="icons_site">https://icons8.com/</string>
    <string name="title">© Veniamin Petrikovskyi, 2024</string>
    <string name="day">Day %d</string>
    <string name="summary1">Professional Advice</string>
    <string name="desc1">Consult with a degreed exercise professional and your private physician prior to starting an exercise program.</string>
    <string name="summary2">Cardio</string>
    <string name="desc2">Get 30 minutes of cardiovascular exercise 5 days a week, minimum.</string>
    <string name="summary3">Water</string>
    <string name="desc3">Drink plenty of water throughout the day, especially while exercising.</string>
    <string name="summary4">Abdominals</string>
    <string name="desc4">Strengthen your core by exercising your abdominals 2 or 3 times a week.</string>
    <string name="summary5">Stretching</string>
    <string name="desc5">Increase your flexibility with dynamic stretching before exercise and static stretching afterwards.</string>
    <string name="summary6">Proper Footwear</string>
    <string name="desc6">Buy shoes that fit and are for your specific exercise. Shop for shoes late in the day when your feet tend to be their largest and find shoes with a ½” of space in front of your longest toe.</string>
    <string name="summary7">Make an Appointment</string>
    <string name="desc7">Schedule your workout into your daily calendar.</string>
    <string name="summary8">Shake Things Up</string>
    <string name="desc8">Change your workout every two months to keep things fresh.</string>
    <string name="summary9">Nutrition</string>
    <string name="desc9">Learn to correctly read nutrition labels. Low fat and no fat aren’t always the best options. These tend to have higher levels of sugar and aren’t necessarily healthy options.</string>
    <string name="summary10">Massage</string>
    <string name="desc10">Reward yourself with a massage.</string>
    <string name="summary11">Strength</string>
    <string name="desc11">Include strength training in your program. It has a multitude of benefits besides adding mass.</string>
    <string name="summary12">Stay Off The Scales</string>
    <string name="desc12">These are not always an accurate measurement of your progress. You could be losing fat but gaining lean muscle thus losing inches but not necessarily losing pounds.</string>
    <string name="summary13">Keep a record</string>
    <string name="desc13">Test yourself often. Every 4 weeks measure a variable such as body fat percentage, weight or amount of weight lifted that equates to your end goal. The gains, or losses, are great motivators.</string>
    <string name="summary14">Alcohol</string>
    <string name="desc14">Reduce Alcohol Consumption. A single beer has anywhere from 100 to 150 empty calories.</string>
    <string name="summary15">Goals</string>
    <string name="desc15">Set Goals. Use the SMART approach. (Specific, Measurable, Attainable, Realistic and Timely)</string>
    <string name="summary16">Soft drinks</string>
    <string name="desc16">Replace one soft drink a day with a glass of water, with the end goal being one soft drink a day.</string>
    <string name="summary17">Don\'t overtrain</string>
    <string name="desc17">Don’t overdo it. Overtraining leads to injuries.</string>
    <string name="summary18">Rest</string>
    <string name="desc18">Get plenty of rest. A goal of a minimum of seven hours of sleep a night.</string>
    <string name="summary19">Meals</string>
    <string name="desc19">Avoid “man-sized” meals. Instead of two to three large meals aim for five to six small meals to maintain metabolism.</string>
    <string name="summary20">Active rest</string>
    <string name="desc20">Plan active rest. Take at least two days a week and engage in activities other than your workout plan.</string>
    <string name="summary21">Outside</string>
    <string name="desc21">Get outside. Fresh air and sunshine help reduce stress and can be motivational.</string>
    <string name="summary22">Fiber</string>
    <string name="desc22">Eat more fiber. Fiber makes you feel full, improves your cholesterol and aids in digestion.</string>
    <string name="summary23">Salt and fat</string>
    <string name="desc23">Cut back on salt and fatty foods. Choose lean meats and fresh fruits and vegetables over canned whenever possible.</string>
    <string name="summary24">Dressing in salad</string>
    <string name="desc24">Dressing on the side. Instead of dousing your salad with dressing request it served on the side. Dip you fork into the dressing and then into your salad. The calorie savings will shock you.</string>
    <string name="summary25">Reps</string>
    <string name="desc25">Do the right reps for you. Lower reps for power, strength and size and higher reps for endurance, toning and weight loss.</string>
    <string name="summary26">Numbers</string>
    <string name="desc26">Know your numbers. Keep active records of your blood pressure, body weight and cholesterol levels to name a few.</string>
    <string name="summary27">Heart rate</string>
    <string name="desc27">Use your heart rate to measure your intensity not the amount of sweat.</string>
    <string name="summary28">Partner Up</string>
    <string name="desc28">To increase accountability workout with someone else, hire a personal trainer or participate in a group exercise class.</string>
    <string name="summary29">Have fun</string>
    <string name="desc29">Pick cardiovascular exercises you enjoy to increase your enjoyment. People tend to stop doing things that they don’t enjoy, so pick one that fits your personality.</string>
    <string name="summary30">Plan meals</string>
    <string name="desc30">Plan meals ahead of time. This will allow you to make healthier choices and avoid the drive through lane.</string>
</resources>